sentimentrader.com 2013-12-27

# Why Bonds

PRIVACY POLICY

* * *

Sundial Capital Research, Inc. is committed to keeping your personal information secure.  Please read the information below to become familiar with our policies regarding your information and the sentimenTrader.com web site.

**Use of Information**

sentimenTrader.com gathers personal information in the process of verifying your identity when subscribing to the service.  Such information includes name, address, credit card details (for billing purposes) and email address.  **_Under no circumstances is any personal information, including but not limited to name, address, credit card and email address shared or sold to any non-essential outside parties_**.  The release of limited personal information to outside parties is needed to validate against fraud in the case of subscription payments, verify access to the subscriber's section of the web site and allow our credit card processing company to charge the appropriate credit card.  Sundial Capital Research, Inc. may also disclose information about our users when we believe, in good faith, that the disclosure is required by law. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user, which is created when a user subscribes to the service.  We use cookies to store subscribers' user names and passwords so that they do not have to input these items every time they visit our web site.  At any time, you may delete the cookie from your web browser, however such action will require you to log in each time you visit the site.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to display a warning before accepting a cookie, or to refuse all cookies, or to accept cookies only from certain web sites (see your browser's "help" menu for more information). However, if you choose to disable the receipt of cookies from sentimenTrader.com, you may not be able to use certain features of the site. 

**Log Files**  
Like most web hosting services, our web host compiles general log files of user traffic. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks.  This allows us to monitor site traffic in a broad sense.  In no way is any personal information shared or stored in regard to these log files.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on our website are delivered to our customers by our web advertising partners. Information about our users' visits to the site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not personal information), is used to serve ads to users on our website.  sentimenTrader.com may derive revenue from advertising. In order to attract and retain advertisers we may use the aggregated, anonymous information that we gather (as well as information from third-party market researchers) to describe our services to partners and to assist our advertisers and sponsors to better understand our audience. We do not disclose personal information about our users to these parties.  Please be aware that advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may separately collect personal information about you. The information practices of those parties and web sites linked to sentimenTrader.com are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**Emails**  
We send all new subscribers a welcome e-mail to verify password and username. All subscribers receive regular emails when a comment is posted to sentimenTrader.com.  Subscribers may opt in to receive other emails that are a part of the service.  If a subscription is cancelled, email address are removed from our mailing lists and are not used for external marketing purposes.  At any time, subscribers may request to be removed from any and all mailing lists, while still maintaining access to the web site.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve customer privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

**Security**  
When customers submit sensitive information via our website, their information is protected both online and off-line.  When our registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL (Secure Socket Layer). While on a secure page, such as our order form or "Update Information" page among others, the lock icon on the bottom of web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, identifying the page as secure. 

**Your Consent To This Agreement**

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by Sundial Capital Research, Inc. as specified above.  Any changes to our policy will be posted promptly on this page.

If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact us.

Sundial Capital Research, Inc.

12527 Central Avenue NE, Suite 165

Blaine, MN  55434

Toll-free phone:  888-795-9893

E-mail:  [admin@sentimentrader.com](mailto:admin@sentimentrader.com)
